# Jesus Popocatl Lara

## Game Developer

★ Mexico City, Mexico

popocatl22@live.com.mx

(044) 55 3445 3274

popocatldev.wixsite.com

in linkedin.com/in/popocatl

#### **EDUCATION**

Facultad de Ingeniería, UNAM

Computer Engineering | 2012 - 2016

#### **TECNOLOGIES**

- C#
- C++
- Python
- Java
- Javascript
- HLSL
- HTML/CSS
- SQL

- Unity 3D
- NodeJS
- React|S
- Firebase
- Git
- Jira

#### SKILLS

- OOP
- Agile
- Design Patterns
- SOLID
- Game Design

#### SUMMARY

Game Developer with over 4 years of experience in the game industry. Collaborated with designers and artists to develop and deploy projects for mobile and web. Specialized in game programming and Unity3D, also have knowledge in Shaders and Web Development. I look for a position as a game designer or gameplay programmer.

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## **Game Programmer**

Big Monster | 2017 - 2022

- Programming of gameplay mechanics, Al and Ul
- Implementation of art, animations and VFX
- Optimization and projects update
- Development of interactive applications
- Contribute with creative ideas and technical solutions

## Software Developer

Desarrollo de habilidades Tecnológicas | 2016 - 2017

• Development of a management software in .NET

## Jr. Game Programmer

Wozlla | 2016

Programming of UI and minor mechanics with Unity and C#

## **GAME JAMS**

Women Game Jam 2019-2020

• Programming Mentor

Global Game Jam 2018-2020

- Programming Mentor
- Participant as Programmer and Game Designer